

LIEN TRAN THI

Front End Developer

About Me

With many years of experience in the accounting profession, along with knowledge and experience gained from Tester and Front-end Developer courses, I hope to become a professional Front-end Developer in the future.

- 038 993 7574
- tranthilien.m@gmail.com
- **å** 26/04/1990
- FPT Plaza1 Building Da Nang
- https://github.com/lientran1990

Certificate

Frontend Developer

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/ 11VfbwqFTrsZ_vppccr1TIKCI68x4M3-q? usp=sharing

Tester

https://drive.google.com/file/d/lskl3cpGEaWgAgeEhc4ZmlFpyY7tYVkQt/view

Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React, Figma
- Git, GitHub
- Manual & Automation Test (Jira Selenium, Postman, SQL)
- Willingness to learn
- Hard-working
- Commitment to excellence and self-improvement

Education

Meta Front-end Developer

07/2023-now

Coursera

- Introduction to Front-End Development
- Programming with JavaScript
- Version Control
- HTML and CSS in depth
- React Basics
- Advanced React
- Principles of UX/UI Design

Software Tester Specialization 09 Funix

09/2022-06/2023

- Introduction to software testing
- Basic testing
- Advanced testing
- Automated testing
- Become a professional programmer

Accountant

09/2019-06/2013

Da Nang University of Economic

Projects - Assignment

- https://lientran1990.github.io/portfolio-reactjs/
- https://lientran1990.github.io/net-gross-calculation/
- https://github.com/lientran1990/MyProjects

Experience

Accountant Payable

02/2020-02/2021

American International Hospital

I have been responsible of overseeing and managing the financial transactions associated with accounts payable within the organization.

General Accountant

03/2015 - 06/2019

Tam Tri Hospital

Streamlining financial transactions, tracking expenses, and ensuring compliance for optimal fiscal management.